Drowning in my shame!
(Aw shit!)
🎶
(What a joke)
A couple thoughts rinsing loosely 'round my head
No escape, can't relate to this--
(Indescribable dread)
SO lather them up and don't question what's ahead
(Liar)
things aside, you've left inside as they prepare to-
FIRE!
Calm waters below
Watch close as they ebb and flow
They're rushing in the wrong direction
What's another crazy obsession?
Now take a dunk in the dunk tank!
Take a look around
The duct tape's holding me alone
I'm soaked in shame down to the bone
Keep your phones out for flash photography
A splash of lukewarm mockery is
all
I
need
to
drown
in everybody's shame!!
🎶
(oh, uh okay so you're just gonna-) OH, COME ON!
Head full of thoughts flood above my mental brim
Insanity
Calamity
It's all pitched on a whim
(BAM!)
Right on the mark!
Where's your damn apology?
(Kill it)
competition
ammunition locked
but here's the key!
Exclude you with power
You're dead in an hour
They won't understand why they're mad - (at you! mad at you!) - anymore
They'll say in good faith
Their guilt is dehydrated
Feel just like a human again
When you make the time to get a
Person you think is lesser than
Kicked on the ground when they couldn't fucking stand!
So take a dunk in the dunk tank!
Take a look around
I'm past my goddamn freezing point
I'll boil off my disappointment
Check my temp and add some salt in
While you cook me in a coffin cuz that's
all
I
need
to
drown
in everybody's--
SHAME!
🎶
(If you mess up, there aren't do-overs here!)
(It's life or fucking death!)
Condensating
Overrating
Feeling both my lungs deflating
Overflowing, barely showing
See-through sea-like tides are flowing
Pull the cord and watch me spiral
Sinking quick - don't check my vitals!
My emotions start to rise like
your devotion to my despise!
(Woah, woah, woah! Nothing personal, but....
...is this what you're after?)
Now take a dunk in the dunk tank
Sponges take the blame
No matter how soft or absorbent
Are you not the most important?
Ring me out in front of everyone
Insults are dry, but you're not done so
take
a
fucking
bow.
Then end it
all in the dunk tank!
Water's still and cold
Whether or not the party's over
Water down my pains exposure
Miss my target, paint a new one
Think and pray for what you're going through so
come
and
watch
my
shallow
cries!
🎶
I'M LYING!
On my back, arms out and stretched
My mercy's all that's left and etched and
Even though my reputation's
Water boarding all my stationed
Ins and outs and woahs and doubts
Despite my pleading and my shouts I'll
cut
my
breath
short
now.